Guide to the Transgender Erotic Pulp Fiction Collection from the Series Gender Bender
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
Transgender erotic pulp fiction collection from the series Gender bender
1998-1999
Bailey 8
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
1
27 v.; 18 cm.
Erotic pulp fiction related to male cross-dressing, forced feminization, and other transgender activity.
Bailey, Laura E., 1951-
Tri Cite/Star Distributors
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Scope and Contents
Erotic pulp fiction related to male cross-dressing, forced feminization, and other transgender activity.
All individual titles paperbound.
Cross-dressers -- Fiction; Cross-dressing -- Fiction; Transgender people -- Fiction; Bisexuals -- Fiction; Sex -- Fiction; Sexual dominance and submission -- Fiction; Erotic stories; Erotica -- New York (State) -- New York -- 20th Century; LGBTQ resource; Bailey, Laura E., 1951- -- Ownership
- Gender Bender
  - TV fantasy, c1998; GB_101_ (Box 101-134)
    Scope and Contents
    Barcode price label on front cover, partially obscuring ill.: Rtn. by 7/14/98 $5.95
  - 10 inch she-male, c1998; GB_103_ (Box 101-134)
    "Binding error; in binding with cover title: TV stewardess Barcode price label on front cover, partially obscuring ill.: Rtn. by 7/14/98 $5.95"
  - TV stewardess, c1998; GB_104_ (Box 101-134)
    "Binding error; in binding with cover title: 10 inch she-male Barcode price label on front cover, partially obscuring ill.: Rtn. by 7/14/98 $5.95"
  - Transvestite mistress, c1998; GB_105_ (Box 101-134)
    Inventory (?) label on front cover: D.A.B. Inc. 634-4705 24
  - TV soap star, c1998; GB_106_ (Box 101-134)
    Price label on front cover: $5.95
  - Belle with balls, c1998; GB_107_ (Box 101-134)
  - TV whipmistress, c1998; GB_108_ (Box 101-134)
    Stamp on bottom edge: Model Dist.
  - TV nun, c1998; GB_109_ (Box 101-134)
  - TV hooker, c1998; GB_110_ (Box 101-134)
  - TV maid, c1998; GB_111_ (Box 101-134)
    Inventory (?) label on front cover: 29 Capitol
  - TV nympho, c1998; GB_112_ (Box 101-134)
    Stamp on top edge: ECN
  - Transvestite tease, c1998; GB_113_ (Box 101-134)
    "Copy 1: Stamp on top edge: MAMG98 Copy 2: Stamp on top edge: 32 [?]"
  - Crossing the line, c1998; GB_114_ (Box 101-134)
    Barcode label on back cover, obscuring printed barcode; Stamp on top edge: ECN.
  - Needing it, c1998; GB_115_ (Box 101-134)
    "Copy 1: Unidentified item affixed to t.p., possibly an anti-theft strip Copy 2: Barcode label on back cover, obscuring printed barcode; Stamp on top edge: ECN"
  - TV training school, c1998; GB_116_ (Box 101-134)
  - Panties with bulges, c1998; GB_117_ (Box 101-134)
    Inventory (?) label on back cover: 37
  - That's no lady, c1998; GB_118_ (Box 101-134)
    Copy 2: Price label on front cover, partially obscuring title: 38 38 for $5.95
  - TV blind date, c1998; GB_119_ (Box 101-134)
    "Stamp on top edge: ECN Blank label or anti-theft device on back cover, obscuring printed barcode"
  - TV undercover, c1998; GB_120_ (Box 101-134)
    Stamp on top edge: 38
  - TV dream, c1998; GB_121_ (Box 101-134)
  - Lady Mike, c1998; GB_122_ (Box 101-134)
    Price label on front cover, partially obscuring ill.: Rtn. by 01/6/99 $5.95
  - Silk and lace, c1998; GB_123_ (Box 101-134)
  - Queen of the soaps, c1998; GB_124_ (Box 101-134)
  - Robyn's little girl, c1999; GB_129_ (Box 101-134)
    Stamp on bottom edge: EST
  - Dreamer, c1999; GB_130_ (Box 101-134)
  - Doc dress-up, c1999; GB_132_ (Box 101-134)
    Price label on front cover: $9.95 The Bedside Table
  - Dressing her boy, c1999; GB_134_ (Box 101-134)